export const questions = [
  {
    id: '1',
    question: '1+1',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    id: '2',
    question: '2+2',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    id: '3',
    question: '4+4',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    id: '4',
    question: '8-3',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    id: '5',
    question: '6*7',
    answer: 42,
  },
  {
    id: '6',
    question: '11/4',
    answer: 2.75,
  },
  {
    id: '7',
    question: '(4+5)*3',
    answer: 27,
  },
  {
    id: '8',
    question: '2*(27-3)/4',
    answer: 12,
  },
  {
    id: '9',
    question: '(15-9)*(7+8)',
    answer: 90,
  },
  {
    id: '10',
    question: '(17+29)/(50/10)',
    answer: 9.2,
  },
  {
    id: '11',
    question: '2*(24+32)/(63-55)',
    answer: 14,
  },
  {
    id: '12',
    question: '340/8',
    answer: 42.5,
  },
  {
    id: '13',
    question: '87*3',
    answer: 261,
  },
  {
    id: '14',
    question: '[69/(12-9)]*5',
    answer: 115,
  },
  {
    id: '15',
    question: '(7*22)/[4*(27-21.5)]',
    answer: 7,
  },
  {
    id: '16',
    question: '50+35',
    answer: 85,
  },
  {
    id: '17',
    question: '40+31',
    answer: 71,
  },
];
